我叫巴里·艾伦  是现今世上速度最快的人
My name is Barry Allen, and I am the fastest man alive.
我年幼时  看到自己的母亲
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
被令人难以置信的东西杀害
by something impossible.
快跑  巴里
Run, Barry, run!
我父亲因为谋杀母亲进了监狱
My father went to prison for her murder.
但是一场事故让我也变得令人难以置信
Then an accident made me the impossible.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但我秘密地用自己的速度打击犯罪
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
寻找跟我一样的人
and find others like me.
终有一天  我会找到杀害母亲的凶手
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother...
-妈妈  -让我父亲沉冤得雪
- Mom! - and get justice for my father.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on The Flash...
黄衣人带走了艾迪
A man in yellow, he took Eddie.
你好  巴里
Hi, Barry.
或者我该叫你闪电侠
Or should I say The Flash?
仔细看看
Observe.
娶到爱瑞丝的是巴里  不是你
Barry marries Iris, and not you.
闪电侠消失于危机中
作者爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦
我一直在做同一个梦
I've been having these dreams.
梦里都发生了什么事
What happens in the dreams?
威尔斯博士就是逆闪电
Dr. Wells is the Reverse-Flash,
而且他还杀了我
and he kills me.
如果这是威尔斯博士
If this is Dr. Wells,
那一直和我们合作的人是谁
then who have we been working for this whole time?
根本就是另外一个人
A completely different person.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我不想杀你  巴里  我需要你
I don't want to kill you, Barry. I need you.
我们很快会再次面对彼此的
We will face each other again very soon.
我希望你能花一点时间
I want you to take a moment,
去想一想那些定义了你人生的事物
and think about all the things that define your life.
你所爱的那些人
All the people you love.
你的工作
Your job.
你的同事
Your coworkers.
你的家
Your home.
现在  想象一下假如有一天
And now imagine if one day,
在一闪之间
in a flash,
所有这些都消失了
all of that vanished.
你会不会简单地
Would you simply
接受新生活继续走下去
accept your new life and continue on?
还是会不惜一切代价
Or would you do whatever it takes...
夺回你所失去的一切
to get back what was taken from you?
因为
Because...
我可以向你保证
I can assure you.
我会夺回一切曾属于...
I will get everything that was taken...
我的东西
from me.
闪电侠  第一季  第二十二集
爱瑞丝·韦斯特与艾迪·斯旺
这些是什么
What's all this?
艾迪和我的回寄标签
Return labels for Eddie and me.
我定了两百个  但是这个下午
I ordered 200 to start, but this afternoon,
送来了两千个
2,000 arrived.
我猜是我下错单了
I guess I ordered wrong.
现在我手上一大堆这个
I have so many now.
爱瑞丝  我们会找到艾迪的
Iris, we're gonna find Eddie.
怎么找
How?
你哪里都找遍了
You searched everywhere.
还不止一次
More than once.
但是却什么都没发现
And you haven't found anything.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没有生你的气
I'm not mad at you.
-只不过...  -你很想他
- It's just... - You miss him.
是的  我想
Yeah, I do.
威尔斯夺走了我妈妈
Wells took my mom from me.
我不会再让他从你身边夺走任何人
I won't let him take someone from you, too.
是西斯科  我得走了
Cisco. I gotta go.
好  去吧
Yeah, go.
我一直问我自己
I kept asking myself,
为什么威尔斯要假装需要轮椅
why would Wells pretend to need a wheelchair?
博同情吧  我猜的
Sympathy, I suppose.
我一开始也是这么想的
That's what I thought at first,
但是他是黄衣人  他是逆闪电
but he's the man in yellow. He's the Reverse-Flash.
他可聪明的很
He's much smarter than that.
博同情不可能是唯一目的
Sympathy can't be the only reason.
那就是种误导
Yeah, it was a misdirect.
就像威尔斯做的其他事一样
Just like everything else Wells has done.
黄衣人最不可能
I mean, the last person we'd suspect to be the man in yellow
是某个腿部残废的人
is someone who lost the use of their legs.
完全正确  乔
That's exactly right, Joe.
这就是为什么我开始研究这轮椅
Which is why I started messing around with the wheelchair.
然后我发现了这个
And that's when I found this.
我去  这东西在无线器材店可买不到
Damn. You can't get that at Radio Shack.
看起来像是用在吉迪恩里的科技
Looks like the tech inside Gideon.
我测量了输出量
I measured the output,
这东西发射着大量的能量
and this thing is kicking off serious juice.
我们谈论的可是能够供应
I mean, we're talking enough to power
整个中城的量
all of Central City.
-真的吗  -没错
- Seriously? - Oh, yeah.
你觉得威尔斯是用它来干什么的
What do you think Wells was using it for?
我觉得这东西是某种电池
I think this thing is some kind of battery.
电池
Battery?
就是威尔斯用来给自己充电的
As in, Wells was using it to power himself.
来获得更快的速度
To gain more speed.
这也是他比你快那么多的原因
And that's why he's so much faster than you.
粒子加速器已启动
加速器  被重新启动了
The accelerator, it's been reactivated.
-这不可能  -这怎么可能呢
- It can't be. - How is that possible?
之前都爆炸了
It blew up.
肯定是被重建过了
It had to have been rebuilt.
-是威尔斯干的  -就算他真的重建了
- Wells. - Even if he did rebuild it,
威尔斯博士是怎么把粒子加速器打开的呢
how did Dr. Wells turn the Particle Accelerator on?
他在这里
He's here.
这就是为什么我们找不到他
That's why we couldn't find him.
他一直在尖端科研实验室里
He's been inside S.T.A.R. Labs the whole time.
待在这别动
Stay here.
西斯科  你带那个橙子汽水来干什么
Cisco, what did you bring in that orange soda for?
只要逆闪电有任何动作
Whenever something happens with the Reverse-Flash,
液体就会在空中悬浮
liquid floats in the air.
巴里的鱼缸  威尔斯的香槟
You know, Barry's fish tank, Wells's champagne,
兰斯的咖啡  你还记得吗
Lance's coffee, remember that?
如果这个原理不变的话
If this does the same thing,
我们就会知道威尔斯是否在这里
we'll know that Wells is in there.
动手吧
Do it.
这地方可真壮观
Man...this...is...big.
天呐
Oh, God.
大伙们...
Guys...
巴里
Barry!
现在要怎么办
Wha-what do we do now?
释放囚犯  程序已启动
Prisoner release. Protocol initiated.
不  不好
Oh, no, no, no, no.
不好
No!
躲猫猫
Peek-a-boo.
你知道被困在那个盒子里
Do you have any idea what it's like
是什么感受吗
to be stuck in that box?
现在换你进盒子里待着了
Now you're the one who's gonna go into a box.
只不过你进的是棺材
In the ground.
-你还好吗  -我会没事的
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I will be.
多亏了爱瑞丝
Thanks to Iris.
你能来真好
I'm glad you showed up.
她是怎么逃出来的
How do you think she got out of there?
肯定是威尔斯把她放出来的
Wells must have released her.
-救命  -等等
- Help. - Wait a sec.
你听见了吗
Did you hear that?
我已经检查过所有的牢笼
I checked all the containment cells.
每个人都还在
Everyone's accounted for.
不  仔细听
No, no. Listen.
救命  在下面
Help! Down here!
救命
Help!
艾迪
Eddie?
天呐  搭档
Oh, partner.
天呐  我找到你了
Oh, my God. I got you.
天呐
Oh, my God.
艾迪  你还好吗
Eddie. Are you okay?
带他离开这里
Let's get him out of here.
走吧
Come on.
好了  慢慢来
There you go. Go slow.
你体征正常
Your vitals are normal,
但有点脱水
but you're just a little dehydrated.
静脉注射能缓解一下情况
The IV should help with that,
不过还要多喝水
but drink some fluids
不要下地运动  行吗  艾迪
and stay off your feet, okay, Eddie?
谢了  凯特琳
Thanks, Caitlin.
没抓住威尔斯
Wells got away.
他太快了
Oh, he was too fast.
他一直都很快
He's always too fast.
艾迪
Eddie.
我们在管道监狱下的甲板找到了他
We found him under that hatch in the pipeline.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我以为我什么地方都找过了
I thought I looked everywhere for you.
这不是你的错
Hey, it's not your fault.
有时候线索不好找
Sometimes you just can't see the clues.
哪怕它们就在你眼前
Even if they're right in front of you.
好吧  总之
Um, well, you know,
最重要的是我们都没事
all that's important is that we're all safe,
而且又在一起了  不是吗
and back together, right?
艾迪  他抓你干什么
Eddie, why did he take you?
我不知道
I don't know.
他说他和我是家人
He said that we're...family.
他说他的真名是艾尔伯德·斯旺
Said his real name was Eobard Thawne.
艾尔伯德·斯旺
Eobard Thawne?
就像我梦中出现过的一样
Just like in my dream.
他还说了别的吗
Did he say anything else?
有没有什么能帮我们弄清楚
I mean, anything that could help us
他真正的目的
figure out what he's really after?
他没说太多话
I--he didn't say much.
就是一直在弄某种管子
He just kept working on some tube.
管子  什么样的
A tube? What did it look like?
金属的  看上去很有未来感
Metallic, futuristic.
他说那是让他夺回
He said it was the key to him
他所失去的一切的关键
getting back everything that was taken from him.
关键  我不明白
The key? I don't understand. Wha--
我也不清楚  我只是想回家
Yeah, I don't know. Look, I just want to go home.
-可以吗  -当然了
- Is that okay? - Yes, of course.
我会让他好好休息的
I'll make sure he gets some rest.
好的
Okay.
你觉得威尔斯说的是什么
What do you think Wells was talking about?
不  不
Oh, no, no, no.
怎么了
What?
现在又有什么问题
What now?
你看见这个了吗
Um, are you seeing this?
那就是艾迪说的管子
That's the tube Eddie was talking about.
这好像是某种来自未来的力量源
It's some sort of future power source.
就是它给粒子加速器充的电
That's what's charging up the accelerator.
你能把它关上吗
Can you shut it down?
你有在上边看到开关吗
Do you see a power button anywhere on this thing?
哥们  这东西来自未来
Dude, this thing is from the future.
比我先进多了  我乱按
It's beyond me. I press,
乱摸或者剪错了东西
or touch, or cut the wrong thing,
整栋楼都会被炸毁
I could bring the whole building down.
好吧  还有多久它才会完全启动
Okay. How long until it's fully functional?
我觉得  大概36小时
Best I can tell, 36 hours.
那也是威尔斯回来的时候
That's when Wells will be back.
为什么威尔斯想让粒子加速器重新运行
Why would Wells want the Particle Accelerator to work again?
我不知道  我们第一次又不是大获成功
I don't know. It's not like it was such a big success the first time.
那次让我成为了闪电侠
It made me The Flash.
这还不止
That's not all it did.
如果粒子加速器重新启动的时候
So what happens if the Particle Accelerator turns on
超能力者还被关在在密闭牢房里会怎样
while the meta-humans are in their containment cells?
他们会被烤焦
They're toast.
是我们把他们关在那里
We put them down there
现在他们生命危在旦夕都是因为我们
and now their lives are in danger because of us.
我觉得你们都知道
Look, I think you all know
我从来都不赞成这里的安排
I've never been a fan of this arrangement here.
我以为这整个计划是让他们恢复原样
I thought the whole plan was to rehabilitate them
然后把他们放走
and set them free.
本来是  我们有点小忙
It was. We've been a little busy.
如果他们在这  结局是死
Well, if they stay in there, they die.
如果放他们走  他们会毁了这个城市
And if we let them go, they destroy the city.
我们要转移他们
We're gonna have to move them.
转去哪
Move them where?
铁山监狱关押不了超能力者
Iron Heights can't handle meta-humans.
你说得对  但是炼狱岛可以
You're right, but Lian Yu can.
炼狱岛是什么
What the hell's a Lian Yu.
炼狱岛是囚禁了奥利弗五年的一座小岛
Lian Yu is the island where Oliver was stranded for five years.
天眼会秘密在那建立了一个军队监狱
A.R.G.U.S built a covert military prison on it.
回旋镖队长就被送去了那
It's where we sent Captain Boomerang.
奥利弗把他最凶恶的罪犯送去那
Oliver keeps his worst criminals there.
他们逃脱不了  更重要的是
They won't be able to escape, and more importantly,
他们没办法伤害到其他人
they won't be able to hurt anybody.
好嘛  那就是我们把他们从一个非法黑监狱
Great. So we ship them from one illegal black site
送到另一个
to another?
对  我觉得是这样  没错
Yeah, I guess so. Yes.
我们怎么把他们转移到
And how do we move them to
奥利弗自己的阿尔卡特拉斯岛
Oliver's own private Alcatraz?
美国加利福尼亚州西部的一岩石岛屿  曾为军事监狱  现为游览地
我会打电话给他  也许他能帮忙转移
I'll call him. Maybe he can help with transport.
西斯科
And Cisco...
如果我们这么做  你要看紧他们
if we do this, nobody can get loose.
我也许有能把他们安全从这里转移出去的方法
I might have a way of getting them out of here safely.
好的  去做吧
All right, get on it.
巴仔  这太疯狂了
Barr, this is insane.
乔  我们一定要这么做
Joe, we have to do this.
你不会觉得我们运送
You don't think that if we start
这群超级恶棍穿过市区的时候
bussing super-villains through downtown,
没人会注意到吧
nobody's gonna notice?
他们会注意到
Oh, they'll notice.
那时候就需要你出手了
That's where you'll come in.
中城警局
塞西尔
Cecile.
我最爱的地检今天过得怎么样
How's my favorite D.A.?
谢谢你能来
Thanks for stopping by.
我愿为我最爱的警探赴汤蹈火
Hey, anything for my favorite detective.
有什么需要我帮忙
So what can I do for you?
你在电话上听上去有点神秘
You sounded a little cryptic on the phone.
对  我想要听你的意见
Yeah, I wanted your opinion on something.
那些有能力的人  超能力者
These people with powers, the meta-humans.
他们是这么称呼自己的吗
Is that what they're calling them?
人们真是喜欢贴标签
People love their labels.
这么假设来说吧
Yes. Let's say, hypothetically,
我知道有个类似监狱的地方
I know a prison of sorts,
能为铁山监狱所不能为
a place that can do what Iron Heights can't.
这些超能力者  这些坏人
Where these meta-humans, the bad ones,
会被关起来
are being locked up.
我会很担心
I would be very concerned.
特别是  假如
Especially if, hypothetically,
你跟这一切有关的话
you had anything to do with it.
你为什么问我这些
Why are you asking me about this?
因为辛格在度蜜月
Well, because Singh's on his honeymoon,
而你是我唯一可以信赖的人
and you're the only other person I can trust to know this.
好  你想让我做什么
Okay, what are you asking me to do?
我需要在市里清道
I need to clear a route through the city.
路障  警车之类的
Barricades, police cars, the works.
我要跟别人怎么说
What am I supposed to tell people?
总统来了
The President's in town?
我不知道  你觉得他们会信吗
I don't know. You think they'll believe you?
不  乔  不  他们不会的
No, Joe, no. They wouldn't.
你要做的
What you're doing,
叫做非法监禁和偷运人口
it's called unlawful imprisonment and human smuggling.
乔  这是很严重的违法行为
Joe, those are very bad things.
他们是坏人  塞西尔
These are some bad people, Cecile.
但是他们的生命受到了威胁
But their lives are in danger.
我不能参与其中  乔
I can't--I can't get involved in this, Joe.
我不能
I can't.
我是你的朋友  而且很可能在今后
And as your friend, and quite possibly the attorney
成为起诉你的检察官
who will one day be prosecuting you,
我告诉你  离这事越远越好
I'm telling you, get as far away from this as possible.
天眼会有驾运输机
Okay, so A.R.G.U.S. has a transport plane
可以把超能力者带到炼狱岛
that can take the meta-humans to Lian Yu.
我们只要把他们带到费里斯机场
We just need to get them to Ferris Airfield.
然后奥利弗·奎恩来交接
So Oliver Queen came through then?
不  其实不是他来
No. Actually, it was not him.
很显然他正在南达尔巴特
Apparently he's in Nanda Parbat...
-什么  -我也不知道那在哪儿
- What? - Wherever that is. I don't know.
我打给了莱拉  狄格尔的妻子
I called Lyla, Diggle's wife.
她会帮我们搞定
She's gonna hook us up.
所以  中城警局护送我们一程如何
So, what about CCPD giving us an escort?
这事没戏了
Man, it ain't happening.
-什么  -你看到我和地检官说话的情形了
- What?  - You saw me talking to the D.A.
她的态度非常明确
She was very clear.
我可能会丢工作  可能会坐牢
I could lose my badge. I could go to jail.
咱们可能都会坐牢
We could go to jail.
我们  我们在保护别人啊
We--we are protecting people.
是啊  巴里  但我是个警察
We are, Barry, but...I'm a cop.
有一些既定的规矩我得遵守
There's a certain set of rules I need to follow,
而今年  我违反了所有规定
and this year, I broke all of them.
-和我的上司撒谎  -我知道
- Lying to my boss... - I know.
目无法律
Ignoring the law.
什么时候起  我们变得和罪犯
I mean, at what point do we become no different
并无二样了
than the people we're fighting?
我们可太不一样了
We are way different.
怎么不一样
How?
我们违规是为了帮助他人
We only break the rules to help people.
圣人与罪人酒馆
再给我一杯
Give me another one.
要冰冷的
Ice cold.
这不是那位红色极速者吗
If it isn't the scarlet speedster.
咱俩得谈谈
We need to talk.
你想来点什么吗  啤酒  吃的
You want anything? Beer, food?
这儿的腌鸡蛋可是一绝
Pickled eggs here are fantastic.
不  我不饿  我有事需要你的帮忙
No, I'm good. I need your help with a problem.
一定是走投无路了才会来找我帮忙
Must be pretty desperate to come asking for my assistance,
不过我有兴趣  你需要什么
but I'll bite. What do you need?
帮忙把几个人送出城
Help transporting some people out of the city.
几个人
How many?
五个
Five.
五个非常坏的
Five very bad,
非常愤怒的人
very angry people
而且具有超能力
who have powers.
超能力  是吗
Powers, hmm?
所以你想要我做什么  把他们冻住
So you want me to what? Freeze the problem?
在事情不妙时保护你不受他们的伤害
Protect you from them if anything goes wrong?
做生意的第一条要义  永远保护你自己
First rule of business: always protect yourself.
我不会帮忙把你的敌人引出城
I'm not gonna help usher your enemies out of town.
他们不只是我的敌人
Hey, they're not just my enemies.
他们也是你的敌人
They're your enemies, too.
我深表怀疑
I doubt it.
他们会毁灭中城的
They will destroy Central City.
这不关我的事
It's not my problem.
你说过你喜欢这里  这是你的家
You said that you love it here. That this is your home.
我确实爱这里  这也是我家
I do and it is.
但你猜怎么着
Well, guess what?
一旦这些人被放出来
These people get loose,
这个值得被爱的城市就不复存在了
there won't be a city to love anymore.
要是所有人都死了  你也没机会抢劫别人了
You won't be able to rob anyone if everybody's dead.
这是个很有说服力的论点
It's a compelling argument.
但如果我帮了你
But if I'm gonna help you out...
我需要一些回报
I'll need something in return.
-什么回报  -这个
- Like what? - This.
不  这不可能
No. This is impossible.
我做不到
I can't do that.
这样我就帮不了你了
Then I can't help you.
肯定有...
There has to--
史纳特  肯定有什么你想要我也能给的
Snart, there has to be something you want that I can get.
让我想想
Let me think about it.
艾迪
Eddie.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
这儿  工作啊
Here. Work.
你被绑架了将近两个礼拜
You were kidnapped for nearly two weeks
而你想到的第一件事是赶回来工作
and your first thought is to go back to work?
我只是想要生活里有些不变的东西
I just needed something constant in my life.
我以为那是我们
I thought that was us.
艾迪  我想你
Eddie, I miss you.
我爱你
I love you.
当我们找到你时  我看到了这个
I saw this when we found you.
这个是给我的  不是吗
This was for me, wasn't it?
当你把我带到滨水区
When you took me to the waterfront
而威尔斯博士绑架了你时  你是要向我求婚
and Dr. Wells abducted you, you were going to propose.
我当时是
I was.
但现在你不想了吗
But now you're not?
他对你做了什么
What did he do to you?
他什么都没对我做  爱瑞丝
He didn't do anything to me, Iris.
是他给我看的东西
It's what he showed me.
他能给你看什么
What could he possibly have shown you
以至于你会对我们的关系改变心意
that would make you change your mind about us?
未来
The future.
他给我展示了未来  爱瑞丝
He showed me the future, Iris.
我们没有结婚
We don't get married.
你和巴里结婚了
You and Barry do.
听着  我得走了
Look, I gotta go.
你是疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
你说你和莱昂纳多·史纳特谈过了是什么意思
What do you mean you talked to Leonard Snart?
我向他寻求帮助
I asked him for help.
巴里  为什么你要干这么蠢的事
Barry, why would you do something so stupid?
因为  乔  我们已经别无选择了
Because, Joe, we have already tried everyone else.
你问了中城警局  我问了奥利弗
Look, you tried the CCPD. I tried Oliver.
我连罗尼和斯泰因教授都问了
I even tried Ronnie and Dr. Stein.
而且粒子加速器的启动时间是
And the Particle Accelerator goes online in...
16小时后
16 hours.
16小时  乔
16 hours, Joe.
我不能让超能力者这么死掉
I'm not willing to let the metas die,
但也不能让他们逃走
and we can't let them escape, either.
不管承不承认  如果西斯科的办法不行
So, like it or not, Snart, with his cold gun,
史纳特和他的冷冻枪
is the only one that can stop them
就是我们唯一的选择
if Cisco's transportation does not hold.
幸运的是我想到了你能为我做的事
Then lucky for you I figured out what it is you can get me.
你好  警探  很高兴又见面了
Hello, Detective. Nice to see you again.
凯特琳  西斯科
Caitlin, Cisco.
我考虑了你的提议
I thought about your proposal.
你要我帮你  这就是我的条件
You want my help, this is what I want.
我的指纹  牙科记录
My fingerprints, dental records,
基因  犯罪记录  族谱
DNA, criminal records, family tree,
世界上关于莱昂纳多·史纳特的一切信息
everything there is in this world concerning Leonard Snart.
都要销毁
I want it destroyed.
所有的
All of it.
不管是中城警局  网上还是哪里的资料
At CCPD, online, everywhere.
这家伙脸皮可真厚
The brass on this dude.
你真觉得我们会这么做吗
You really think we'd do that for you?
我同意
I'll do it.
如果只能如此  那好
If it's the only way, fine.
你和我现在需要谈谈
You and me need to talk right now.
你怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
你不能就这么抹掉史纳特的犯罪记录
You can't just erase Snart's criminal record.
我可以  而且我会不惜一切代价
Yeah, I can. And I'll do whatever I have to do.
巴里  一定还有别的办法的
Barry, there's gotta be a different way to do this.
好吧  什么办法  乔
Okay, well, what is it, Joe?
你说了  我们就去办
Tell me what it is, and we'll do it.
我们没时间了
We're running out of time!
你到底是怎么了
What is going on with you?
你要和那个杀人犯合作
You working with that killer.
这不是你
This isn't who you are.
我因为不够快所以没法阻止威尔斯
Who I am is the guy who's not fast enough to stop Wells.
他不是超前了我们一步  乔
He--he hasn't been one step ahead of us, Joe.
他超前了我们太多  我抓不到他
He's been 1,000. I can't catch him.
我无法战胜他
I can't beat him.
我能做的  只是救下这里的人
What I can do is save those people down there.
威尔斯把他们变成了这副摸样
Wells turned them into what they are,
我十分确定他一点都不在乎
and I'm pretty sure he does not care
他们的死活
if they live or die.
但我在乎
I do.
中城警局
再见  莱昂纳多·史纳特
Bye-bye, Leonard Snart.
文件删除
我删了所有中城警局
I've deleted everything the CCPD,
天眼会和联调局中你的资料
A.R.G.U.S., and the FBI had on you,
还启动了一个病毒
and sent a virus
删掉了网络上你的所有电子记录
to erase every digital record of you online.
这是警局剩下的
And this is every single piece
所有纸质证据
of physical evidence the police had.
很好
Good.
听说我们要合作了
I hear we're all going to be working together.
没错  妹妹
That's right, Sis.
我们是搭档了
Partners.
请告诉我这是在开玩笑
Please tell me this is a joke.
你说的一点没错  兰尼
Oh, you were right, Lenny.
她真的很暴躁
She is very uptight.
我才不暴躁
I am not uptight.
不许说我暴躁
You can't call me uptight.
各位
Look, guys,
要成功我们就需要他们的帮助
we need their help if we're gonna pull this off.
你干嘛要带上面具
Why are you wearing your mask?
史纳特知道你的身份
Snart already knows who you are.
而且我也保证了不告诉别人
And I promised I wouldn't tell anyone.
其中包括我妹妹
That includes my sister.
混蛋
Jerk.
怪胎
Trainwreck.
不用惊讶  警探
Don't look so surprised, Detective.
我是个守信的人
I am a man of my word.
你最好是
Yeah, you better be.
否则我会把你也丢上那架飞机
Or I'm gonna make sure you're on that damn plane, too.
你好  西斯科
Hey, Cisco.
你好  寒冷队长的邪恶妹妹
Oh, hey, Captain Cold's evil sister.
你不会还在生我的气吧
You're not still mad at me, are you?
我真的挺享受我们接吻的感觉呢
I really did enjoy kissing you.
你亲了她
You kissed her?
那是被迫的  镇定
Under duress. Calm down.
我一直在想你
I've--I've thought a lot about you.
你说真的
Have you really?
那别再想了
Well, stop.
因为我们
Because this right here,
不可能成的
it ain't gonna happen.
想想总可以吧
A girl can hope.
真是不爽
Really not enjoying
这周做个好人
being one of the good guys this week.
不怎么爽
Really not.
哥们儿
Hey, dude.
你想出送那些
Have you figured out a way
超能力者去机场的办法了吗
to get the meta-humans to the airport?
其实还真有个办法
I have, actually.
而且很酷
And it's pretty dope.
真酷  哪弄来的
This is cool. Where'd you get this?
是我叔叔的
My uncle owns it.
他的公司在做国内冷冻食品运输
His company hauls frozen food cross country.
好了  我改进了冷却系统
Okay, so I retrofitted the cooling system
用轮椅的电源
with the wheelchair's power source
制造出一个阻尼器
to create an energy damper.
到底说的都是些什么
Which means what, exactly?
简单来说  这套装备的后面充满了
Basically, the back of this rig is being flooded
巨大的能量  可以有效制造出
with so much power that it's effectively creating
一个瞬间冲力  强大到可以破坏
a transient pulse strong enough to disrupt
超能力者的能力
the meta-humans' powers,
这样就可以把他们送到机场  送上飞机
so we can get them to the airport and get them on a plane
而且会让我们免遭伤害
without them getting fresh on us.
严格来讲  我们需要
Technically, we need somebody
一个有A类商业驾驶员执照的人
with a Class A commercial driver's license
来驾驶这辆车
to drive this, though.
我可以驾驶
I can drive it.
怎么  我有A类商业驾驶员执照
What? I have a Class A CDL.
-你有吗  -不是每个人都能当博士
- You do? - We can't all be doctors.
好吧  行动起来
All right, well, let's do this.
飞机将在两小时后到达
Plane's gonna be here in two hours.
怎么回事
What the hell?
成了  他们都失去知觉了
It's done. They're all unconscious.
阻尼器全方位运行起来了
Dampeners are fully functional.
好的
All right.
我会确保道路通畅
I'll make sure the roads are clear.
不管什么事都别停下
Do not stop for anything.
开始行动
Let's move out.
你先走
After you.
前方有交通堵塞
Hey, we got traffic up ahead.
我来解决
I'm on it.
我们的货物怎么样
How's our cargo doing?
至今为止都挺安静
All quiet so far.
别白费劲了
Don't bother.
你的能力在这里不管用  我们都是如此
Your powers don't work in here. None of ours do.
发生什么事了
What the hell's going on?
他们在移动我们
They're moving us.
去哪
Where?
有趣  我没收到行程安排
Funny, I didn't get an itinerary.
高个子黑头发的帅哥  我说你的能力失效了
Tall, dark, and handsome, I said your powers are offline.
四肢发达  头脑简单
All brawn, no brains.
我认识你  是不是
I know you, don't I?
凯尔·尼比斯
Kyle Nimbus.
曾经是达比尼犯罪家族的一员
Used to be a member of the Darbinyan crime family.
没错
That's right.
一年前你不是被枪决了吗
Weren't you executed about a year ago?
没死成
It didn't take.
不  达比尼家的人不是以
No. The Darbinyans weren't known
雇佣最强最聪明的人而闻名
for hiring the best and brightest.
你连死都出人意料
You couldn't even die right.
看来你现在是非常生气了  马登
So you're so stupid mad right now, Mardon,
你想随便找个人打一架  是吗
you're just going to pick a fight with anyone?
我想是吧
Guess so.
如果现在我有超能力
If I had my powers right now,
我会把你们都毒死
I would gas you all out of existence.
那你将会和四具尸体一起
And then you'd be standing in a container
待在集装箱里
with four corpses.
你会有什么好处
What would that get you?
祥和与安宁
Peace and quiet.
费里斯机场
我不认识你们
Well, I don't know about you guys,
但我不需要超能力
but I don't need my powers
也能把你们都干掉
to fill this rig full of bodies.
来吧
Come on.
怎么回事
What was that?
不管他们要带我们去哪
Wherever they're taking us,
我们已经到了
we're here.
费里斯机场
Ferris Air?
我以为这里已经被关闭了
I thought this place got shut down.
的确是
It did.
他们中的一个试飞员消失了
One of their test pilots disappeared.
计划是什么  我要快点了结此事
So what's the plan? I want to get this over with.
飞机马上就到了
It should be here any minute.
乔  我知道你并不赞同此事...
Look, Joe, I know you don't agree with this--
别说了  巴仔  我只想快点结束
Save it, Barr. I just want to get it done.
你们为什么没给我起个代号呢
How come you haven't given me a code name?
你听说寒冷队长的名字是你起的
I heard you came up with Captain Cold.
你觉得我该叫什么
What do you think I should be called?
女犯人
Female inmate.
拜托
Oh, come on.
你帮我做了枪
You made my gun.
怎么也得给我起个拉风的名字啊
Least you can do is give me a badass alias.
求你了
Please?
好吧
Fine.
金色滑翔者
Golden Glider.
聪明就是性感  西斯科
Smart is sexy, Cisco.
你天眼会的朋友动作很慢啊
Your A.R.G.U.S. friends aren't very prompt.
也许正是如此他们才怎么也抓不到我
Maybe that's why they've never been able to catch me.
他们来了
Look, there it is.
互相攻击并不能解决问题
Turning on each other won't solve anything.
别碰我
Don't ever touch me.
等等
Wait.
你看
Look.
怎么了
What's wrong?
情况不妙
That's not good.
各位  我们有问题了
Guys, guys, we have a problem.
阻尼器在波动
The damper's fluctuating.
装备正失去能量  我不知道怎么回事
The rig's losing power. I don't know why.
等等  你能做点什么吗
Wait, can you do something?
我在努力了
I'm trying.
天呐
Oh, God.
马登干的
Mardon.
行程取消了
Trip's canceled!
呼吸最后一口气吧
Take your last breath!
我要离开这
I'm outta here.
凯特琳  趴下
Caitlin, get down!
你把罗尼关在管道监狱
You locked Ronnie in the pipeline
你杀了罗尼
and you killed Ronnie!
凯特琳  凯特琳  住手
Caitlin, Caitlin, stop!
他杀了罗尼
He killed Ronnie!
-他杀了罗尼  -你在干嘛
- He killed Ronnie! - What are you doing?
干掉他  西蒙斯
Finish him, Simmons.
今晚算平局怎么样
How about we call tonight a tie?
如果你不想毁容  就乖乖投降
I'd power down if you don't want me to melt your face.
我们各走各路
Let's all go our separate ways.
我叫莱昂纳多·史纳特
My name is Leonard Snart.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
总是很乐意见到粉丝
Always pleased to meet a fan.
只需记住是谁保护你们
Just remember who it was made sure
没被扔上那架不知飞往哪里的
you didn't get thrown on that plane
飞机就行
bound for nowhere.
你就这么让我们走吗
You're just letting us go?
你为何朝那家伙开枪
Why'd you shoot that guy?
他欠我钱
He owed me money.
怎么  要我说谢谢吗
What? You want a thank you?
谁不喜欢听道谢呢
Who doesn't like a thank you?
谢谢
Thank you.
千万别客气
You are so very welcome.
你对卡车做了手脚  是吧
You sabotaged the truck, didn't you?
你为什么让他们逃走
Why did you let them escape?
因为现在他们欠了我人情
Because now they all owe me.
直觉告诉我  比起让他们在北海腐烂
And something tells me they'll be a lot more use to me
让他们加入无赖帮
as part of my rogues than rotting away
对我来说更有用
in the North China sea.
你向我保证过了
You gave me your word.
是啊  我保证了
It's true, I did.
但事情是这样的
But here's the thing.
我是个罪犯  骗子
I'm a criminal and a liar,
我伤害人
and I hurt people,
我抢劫他们
and I rob them.
你期望我怎么样  改过自新吗
What did you expect me to do? Not be what I am?
我看到有机会可以对我有利
I saw an opportunity to turn things to my advantage,
我就利用了
and I did.
你真正气的是你自己
Who you're really mad at is yourself.
这都怪你自己  巴里
This is on you, Barry.
那你为什么不直接杀了我
Then why don't you just kill me?
你现在也欠我一份人情了
Well, I guess you owe me one now, too.
祝你
Good luck with...
一切好运
all of this.
其实我很兴奋看到这一切变成这样
I'm actually really excited to see how it all turns out.
再见  西斯科
Bye, Cisco.
西斯科告诉我你在这
Hey, Cisco told me you were in here.
凯特琳怎么样了
How's Caitlin doing?
他在给她光疗
He used that light thingy on her.
她没事
She's fine.
很尴尬
Mostly embarrassed.
是啊
Yeah.
谢谢你没说  我早就跟你说过了
Thanks for not saying, I told you so.
但我确实告诉过你了
But I did tell you so.
很多次
Repeatedly.
我就是
I just...
我见过奥利弗做事的方式
Man, I've seen the way that Oliver does things,
他为了完成目标
and he's not afraid to just do whatever it takes
勇于付出一切代价  我以为我也可以
to get what he needs, and I thought that I could
那么做
do that too.
我以为我可以
I thought I could just
利用史纳特  反过来却是他利用了我
use Snart, but instead he used me.
你不是绿箭  巴里
You're not the Arrow, Barry.
不是
No.
你不是那类英雄
That's not the kind of hero you are.
那我是哪一类
What kind am I?
关心罪犯生死的
The kind that cares about whether or not
那一类
those criminals lived or died.
不管马登  尼比斯和肖恩做过什么
I mean, whatever Mardon and Nimbus and Shawna did,
他们始终是人
they're human beings.
你知道让威尔斯把他们当作人质是不对的
And you knew letting Wells use them as pawns was wrong.
你明是非
You know the difference between right and wrong.
你不愿意去模糊
And you weren't willing to blur the lines
这两者间的界限
between the two.
你是这一类人
That's the kind of man you are.
这就是让你和绿箭不一样的地方
And that's what makes you different than the Arrow.
所以  请你
So, please...
别再游走在邪恶边缘
no more walks on the dark side.
好吗
Agreed?
好
Yeah.
-那是怎么回事  -伙计们
- What the hell is that? - Guys...
粒子加速器完全充满电  开始运转了
The Particle Accelerator is fully charged and online.
不论威尔斯要用它来干嘛
Whatever Wells needs it for,
它都已经准备好了
it's ready.
爱瑞丝  真的没什么好说的了
Iris, there really isn't anything else to say.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
你就因为某个来自未来的疯子
You're going to end this relationship
告诉你我注定要嫁给巴里
because some lunatic from the future
就要结束我们的关系吗
told you that I am destined to marry Barry?
我不相信那个  好吗
Well, I don't believe that, okay?
我相信我们可以选择自己的命运
I believe that we choose our own destiny.
我决定我爱谁  我爱的是你
I decide who I love, and I love you.
不管威尔斯给你看了什么样的未来
Whatever future Wells showed you,
那不是我的未来
it is not my future.
也不是我们的未来
It's not our future.
让我证明给你看吧
Please let me prove it.
这和未来没关系  爱瑞丝
This isn't about the future, Iris.
而是当下
It's about here.
现在  今天
Now. Today.
从一开始起
Ever since the very beginning,
就是三个人纠缠在这段关系中
there's been three people in this relationship.
你  我和巴里
You, me, and Barry.
事情不是这样的
That is not true.
你完全可以否认
You can deny it all you want.
但是巴里知道
But Barry knows it.
乔也知道
Joe knows it.
如果我完全诚实地面对自己
And if I'm gonna be completely honest with myself,
我也会知道
I knew.
我一直都知道
I always knew.
我猜我只是以为
I guess I just...
我对你的爱足以改变一切
thought I could love you enough to change things.
对不起
I'm sorry.
可如果你真的爱我
But if you really do love me,
你就会结束这段关系
you'll let this end.
好吧
Fine.
那就结束吧
Then it ends.
工作功率100%
巴里  千万别去想
Barry, don't even think about it.
巴仔  别
Barr, no.
你不能一个人出去面对
You can't go out there by yourself.
我可以
Yeah, I can.
听说你的转狱不顺利啊
Well, I heard your prison transfer didn't go so well.
非常遗憾
I'm so sorry.
我想这些都是你计划的一部分吧
All a part of your plan, I assume?
其实  那完全不是我计划的一部分
Actually, that didn't factor into my plan at all,
但我很佩服你竭尽全力地
but I'm impressed you went to such great lengths
保护那些人免受伤害
to keep those people from harm.
真是个英雄啊  巴里
Ever the hero, Barry?
你伤害的人已经够多了
You've hurt enough people.
我知道我在你眼中就是坏人
I know. You see me as the villain,
但是  巴里  如果你回头想想
but, Barry, if you were to look back,
回头好好想想
look back carefully
我所做的每一件事
at everything I've done,
我的每一个提议
every wheel I have set in motion,
你就能体会到  我做的这一切
you would realize I have only done
只是我必须要做的而已
what I had to do.
仅此而已
Nothing more.
不多也不少
Nothing less.
那粒子加速器呢
And the Particle Accelerator?
怎么会纳入你的伟大计划中呢
How does that fit into your grand plan?
不如你走进去
Well, why don't you go on inside,
让我告诉你吧
and let me show you.
我已经吸取了教训
You know, I just learned the hard way
不会相信坏人
not to trust the bad guy.
然而
And yet...
我已经一次又一次
I've shown you
向你证明
time and time again
你无法打败我的  巴里
you can't beat me, Barry.
-罗尼  -烈焰风暴
- Ronnie. - Firestorm.
你带来了一个朋友
Wow. You brought yourself a friend.
欢迎啊  奎恩先生
Welcome, Mr. Queen.
希望我们没来得太迟
Hope we're not too late.
来得正好
You're just in time.
我不管你的速度有多快
I don't care how fast you are.
你是无法同时战胜我们三人的
You can't fight all three of us at the same time.
不行吗
Oh, I can't?
相信我
Trust me.
这下一定会很好玩
This, this is gonna be fun.
快出来  巴里
Move, Barry.
巴里  快出来
Barry, move!
来吧
Come on!
罗尼
Ronnie.
雷·帕尔默提供的纳米机器人
Nanites, courtesy of Ray Palmer.
里面正在释放的高频脉冲
They're delivering a high frequency pulse
正在弱化你的速度
that's disabling your speed.
你将有一段时间无法四处跑动了
You're not gonna be running around for quite a while.
历史书上说
The history books say
你会活到86岁  奎恩先生
you live to be 86 years old, Mr. Queen.
看来历史书
Well, I guess the history books
是错的
are wrong.
这样才对
That's the spirit.
你阻止不了我的  闪电侠
You can't stop me, Flash.
永远也不可能
And you never will.
就是现在
Now!
谢谢大家
Thanks, fellas.
不客气
No problem.
发型不错
Nice haircut.
看来你放弃了传统的绿色嘛
And I see we've abandoned our traditional green.
我在尝试不同的事物
Trying something different.
听着
Look...
我可能需要你的帮忙
I might need a favor from you.
随时为你效劳
Wherever, whenever.
抓到你了
I got you.